Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
On the Road
Episode 17
Will the new challenger win?
Or is it the victory of the previous championship?
let’s take a look
The game has been decided
The winner is No. 99 Weslie
Well we won
Was it you who gave me food just now?
No thanks to an old man who looks like Slowy
The vehicle is in hand. Go find Xiao Mei.
Why is it broken?
Done
It turns out that the prize vehicle is actually a vehicle that is almost broken down.
Fortunately, it can still run after repaired.
Let’s go find Xiao Mei now
But I guess Xiao Mei was taken far away
what to do
She can’t run far
I didn’t expect her to show up so soon
Go ahead and tell me what happened next.
Come on, the boss is asking you
She hurt us and then took away our treasures
Then he took the girl and ran to the east.
Are you sure it’s her?
That’s right, that’s right
She uses Sand Shadow on her hand
thank you for your message
Blue Scarf
The grudge between you and me, Cha Erlang, should be resolved.
Let’s go
Did you hear that? He seems to be going after Blue Scarf.
Just follow them
Maybe we can find Xiao Mei
Didn’t they say set off? Why did they run into the house?
Is it an earthquake?
It’s bigger than Sirius
Set off
we chase
Where are Weslie and Wolffy?
Mr. Slowy, hurry up to find them faster.
Weslie
But where is my Wolffy?
Save Weslie first and then talk about it
Mr. Slowy, get out of the way
Move quickly
Oops
Weslie, turn sharply to the right
Finally caught up
full speed ahead
As expected, scrapped vehicles cannot be put on the road.
They never stopped
Why did the vehicle suddenly break down? Where is the engineer?
What
The engineer has slipped out of the bubble
Why don’t you get him back quickly?
yes
Their vehicle is also broken.
With that kind of impact, it’s no wonder it’s damaged.
How about we help them fix their vehicle
and then ask for a ride?
Can you even fix this kind of vehicle?
How will you know if you don’t try?
What are you doing? Sneaky.
Say it quickly
We know your vehicle broke down
So we want to help you fix your vehicle
Then we hope you can take us with you to find Blue Scarf
Because we also want to deal with her
The enemy of my enemy is my friend
Boss, they were the ones who stole the vehicle and Xiao Mei back then.
don’t believe them
What a coincidence
How dare you spoil my good deeds? Drag them down to feed the fish
Where did the fish come from in the desert?
There really is
Finally caught up
Mr. Slow, Weslie and Wolffy are in danger
Weslie here I come
Wolffy it’s your old friend
let us go
Okay, throw them down
Boss, the engineer is unconscious
and won’t wake up for a while
I can help you fix your vehicle
Boss, he has actually helped us repair our vehicle before.
How about we make use of him?
About to be eaten
Your friend will stay here for now
If it can’t be repaired within an hour, then feed him to the fish.
No, Weslie has to be with me
The clock has started
Wolffy I believe you
All right
These devices are too complicated, right?
Be careful, the engineer just stepped on the bubble and slipped out.
Jay
During the time I’ve been here
You’re the first person to remember my name
Wait, how do you know my name?
No time to explain now
Since you’re here
Do you recognize these devices? Tell me quickly how to fix them.
Then you have asked the right person. My second uncle once told me
If something is broken, just pat it and it’ll be fine
stop
I’d better do it myself
All right
After researching for a long time, I feel like there is just something wrong here.
What’s missing here
Can you please stop disturbing me?
I’m sorry. No one has taken the initiative to talk to me since I joined until today.
They all dislike me for always making mistakes
Finally, I was assigned to clean the vehicle
That’s why I want to help you
So there are so many bubbles here because you clean them
No, everyone has a place to shine
As long as you work hard
Someone will notice you one day
real
Yes, you see this part, under your cleaning
How sparkling it has become
Finally discovered by you
I will disassemble every part here and clean it carefully.
Just do everything well
I can definitely become the boss’s most trusted subordinate
Missing parts found
But it turns out it was all because of you
It would be nice if I could rescue Weslie anyway.
Oops, no time
It seems like your friend is not very good.
You will fall when the time is up
Wolffy
Just plug the parts back in and you’ll be fine
What’s going on?
Being conscientious, I washed the inside too
What
Wolffy
Weslie I made it
Bravo Wolffy
You’ve got some skills, haven’t you?
but
Weslie
Why do you want to scare us?
You scared our driver earlier
Why don’t I take the opportunity to take revenge?
Since you helped us again, let’s go on the road together
Finally we can continue on the road
boss, to prevent fraud
Why don’t you ask them why they are also chasing Blue Scarf?
No need to ask. Everyone has different reasons.
No need to delve into it
What should we do? What should we do?
Mr. Slowy, let us go save Weslie.
Sure
But I have other tasks scheduled
So you have to divide into two teams and set off
Mr. Slowy, Mr. Slowy Let me save Weslie
Paddi, why are you so eager this time?
Because Mr. Slowy gave me this new weapon
I can’t wait to try it
Mr. Slowy, then let me go with Paddi.
Okay
Then Wolffy, I’ll leave it to you two.
Brother Paddi, Brother Sparky
come on
it’s time
It’s our turn to show off our skills
To be continued